Calinescu, Matei mss., 1959-2009 LMC 2836
Lilly Library
- Correspondence
  - Personal, Friends and Family, 1959-2009
    - Calinescu, Irena., 1975, July 31 - 2009, May 18 (Box 5)
    - Gelehrter Luigina., 1977, Mar 15 (Box 5)
    - Ghestin, Claudia (Soso)., 1978-2009, June 15 (Box 5)
    - Pascot Marina (Ina)., 1974, Oct 24 - 1982, Dec 21 (Box 5)
    - Pascot Marina (Ina)., 1983, Jan 30 - 1989, Dec 11 (Box 5)
    - Pascot Marina (Ina)., 2001, Oct 1 - 2009, June 15 (Box 5)
    - Pencovici Evelyn (Evy)., 1974, Oct 14 - 1988, Mar 19 (Box 5)
    - Vulcanescu, Mihu., 1987, Jan 20 - 1991, Nov 16 (Box 5)
    - Various., 1976, June 16 - 2007, Feb 14 (Box 5)
    - Mircea Andrei., 1969, Mar 2 - 1999, Sept 17 (Box 5)
    - Various., 1959-2009, Mar 18 (Box 5)
- Diaries
  - Diary 0 (Caietul 0)., 1959; 1961; 1964, Aug 16 - 1965, Jan 8 (Box 7)
  - Diary 1 (Caietul I). Annex 1 & 2, 1973, Apr - May; 1974, May; 1977, May 4 (Box 7)
  - Diary 2 (Caietul II). Annex 1 & 2, 1977, May 7 - Sept 20 (Box 7)
  - Diary 3 (Caietul III). Annex 1, 1977, Dec 27 - 1980, Feb 14 (Box 7)
  - Diary 5 (Caietul V)., 1980, Dec 04 - 1981, Oct 04 (Box 7)
  - Diary 6 (Caietul VI). Annex 1, 1981, Dec 16 - 1982, Sept (Box 7)
  - Diary 7 (Caietul VII)., 1982, Oct 11 - 1985, June 28 (Box 7)
  - Diary 8 (Caietul VIII). Annex 1, 1985, June 29 - 1986, July 17 (Box 7)
  - Diary 9 (Caietul IX)., 1987, Mar 28 - Aug 18; 1988, Jan 14 (Box 7)
  - Diary 10 (Caietul X). Annex 1, 1987, Nov 16 - 1988, Dec 29; 1989, Mar 20 (Box 7)
  - Diary 11 (Caietul XI). (typed diary), 1996, July 22 - Aug 08 (Box 7)
  - Diary 12 (Caietul XII)., 1996, Oct - 1997, July - Aug; 1998, Sept (Box 7)
  - Diary 13 (Caietul XIII)., 1999, Apr - 2000, Apr (Box 7)
  - Diary 14 (Caietul XIV)., 2000, May - 2002, Dec (Box 7)
  - Diary 15 (Caietul XV - English)., 1991, Aug 29 - 1998, Jan 17 (Box 7)
  - Diary 16 (Caietul XVI)., 2009, Mar 10 - June 07 (Box 7)
- Publications Lists, Book Lists (Box 8)
  Includes a CD-ROM. This file also contains lists of Calinescu's and others' typed lists of books, rare books, publications, and presentation books.